Guide to The Packer Collegiate Institute records 2014.019
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 6: Administrative committees and reports, 1846-1997
  - Sub-series 6.2: Administrative reports, 1846-1997; 0.8 Cubic Feet in three boxes
    This sub-series contains assorted administrative reports of the Brooklyn Female Academy and Packer Collegiate Institute, dating from 1846 to 1997.
    - Brooklyn Female Academy reports, 1846-1851 (Box 507, Folder 10)
      Includes Act to Incorporate; by-laws; address delivered at the opening of the school; circulars and catalogues; commencements; and Instructions from the Regents of the University to several colleges ...
    - School Regulations, 1895-1901 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Audio-visual and field trip reports, 1938-1970 (Box 508, Folder 1)
    - Reports: Student officers, group trips, visual information, and non-acceptance of transfer credits, 1947-1949 (Box 508, Folder 2)
    - 125th Anniversary Report from the President to Alumnae, Parents, Students, Staff, and Friends of The Packer Collegiate Institute, 1970 (Box 507, Folder 5)
    - Report on street crimes, 1974 (Box 508, Folder 3)
    - Test results and college statistics, 1978-1988 (Box 508, Folder 4)
    - Math - Science programs, 1980-1981 (Box 508, Folder 5)
    - Self Evaluation report (1 of 4), 1985 (Box 507, Folder 6)
    - Self Evaluation report (2 of 4), 1985 (Box 507, Folder 7)
    - Self Evaluation report (3 of 4), 1985 (Box 507, Folder 8)
    - Self Evaluation report (4 of 4), 1985 (Box 507, Folder 9)
    - Report on Ancient Roman artifacts held by Packer, 1986 (Box 508, Folder 6)
    - Health Department presentation, 1997 (Box 508, Folder 7)
  - Sub-series 6.3: Administrative notes, circa 1900-1949; 0.2 Cubic Feet in four folders
    The sub-series contains miscellaneous administrative notes, dating from circa 1900 to 1949.
    - Administrative notebook, circa 1900-1930 (Box 512, Folder 1)
      Includes meeting minutes, lists of class officers, memoranda, registers, faculty salaries, and other material.
    - Packer objectives and purpose, 1949 (Box 512, Folder 2)
    - Library organization and notes, 1949 (Box 512, Folder 3)
    - Institutional organization, 1949 (Box 512, Folder 4)
- Series 7: Financial records and Annual Reports, 1845-2014; 3.5 Cubic Feet
  Sub-series 7.1: Annual Reports
  Sub-series 7.2: Financial records
  Sub-series 7.3: Pension Fund Committee
  The series contains financial records, annual reports, and the records of the Pension Fund Committee, dating from 1845 to 2014.
  The 1847 Annual Report and Treasurer's Report of the Brooklyn Female Academy is filed with it's Act of Incorporation in Series 1: Charters and By-laws.
  - Sub-series 7.1: Annual Reports, 1849-1850, 1938-2014; 1.1 Cubic Feet in nine boxes
    This sub-series contains Packer Collegiate Institute annual reports, dating from 1938 to 2014.
    The reports include a variety of information in addition to financial matters, such as additions to the pre-existing curriculum and field trips intended to prepare students for the SAT exam (1950-1951), which was introduced in 1949 by the College Exam Board. A report from 1938-1968 includes information regarding male admissions, added courses, extracurricular activities, and the damages from the 1964 fire.
    The series includes two annual reports of the Brooklyn Female Academy (1849 and 1850).
    - Annual Report of Brooklyn Female Academy, 1849 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings of Stockholders and Annual Report of the Brooklyn Female Academy, 1850 (Box 566, Folder 10)
    - Reports of the President to the Trustees, 1938-1939 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Report of the President to the Board of Trustees, 1938-1968 (Box 506, Folder 15)
    - Financial Statements and Reports to Board of Trustees, 1938-1975 (Box 476, Folder 5)
    - Reports of the President to the Trustees, 1939-1945 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Report of the President to the Board of Trustees, 1945-1946 (Box 506, Folder 16)
    - Reports of the President to the Trustees, 1945-1954 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Report of the President to the Board of Trustees, 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Report of the President to the Board of Trustees, 1954-1955 (Box 506, Folder 17)
    - Report of the President to the Trustees, 1955-1961 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Report of the President to the Trustees, 1961-1965 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Report of the President to the Trustees, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Report of the President to the Trustees, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Report of the President to the Trustees, 1938-1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Report of the President to the Trustees, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Report of the President to the Trustees, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Report of the President to the Trustees, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Report of the President to the Trustees, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Report of the President to the Trustees, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Packer Magazine with 1990-1991 Annual Report inside (Box 476, Folder 10)
    - Annual Reports, 1991-1996 (Box 476, Folder 11)
    - Annual Reports, 1993-1996 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports, 1996-1998 (Box 476, Folder 13)
    - Annual Reports, 1998-2001 (Box 476, Folder 14)
    - Annual Reports, 2001-2003 (Box 477, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 2003-2006 (Box 477, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 2011-2014 (Box 477, Folder 3)
  - Sub-series 7.2: Financial records, 1845-1994; 2.25 Cubic Feet in eight boxes
    The sub-series contains assorted financial records, dating from 1845 to 1994. It contains fundraising and administrative budget materials, including ledgers for the Mrs. Packer Memorial Window Fund, 1906-1909; Treasurer's Reports, 1912-22; and the Administrative Budget, 1922-1934. It includes typewritten and bound minutes of Packer's Committee on Finance, 1951-1968; and an itemized valuation of the Institute's stock holdings as of February 2, 1955, which summarizes the division of the school's $938,761.00 market investment, the bulk of which was committed to government bonds, public utilities, and chemical stocks. Other materials include a cash ledger, 1892-1904; the ledger for the Memorial Window fund, 1905-1906; the Backus Memorial Fund account book, 1908-1909; a plea for funds letter signed collectively by the board of trustees, 1917; Packer alumni pledge cards, 1917; an Endowment fund ledger, 1917-1921; check stubs, 1926-1932; and Centennial Fund documents, 1945-1961. The series also contains student tuition bills, 1866-1916.
    Related records can be found in Series 12: Development Office, Fund Raising, and Alumni records.
    - Stock payment receipts, 1845 (Box 475, Folder 7)
      Brooklyn Female Academy Receipts of Payment for Stockholders (April 1845 to 17 July 1845)
    - Stock certificates, 1845-1853 (Box 475, Folder 8)
      Brooklyn Female Academy Stock Certificates (1 September 1845 to 15 January 1853)
    - Stock Dividend Payment Receipts, 1845-1854 (Box 475, Folder 9)
      Dividend Payment Receipts (8 December 1845 to 3 February 1854)
    - Miscellaneous Financial Documents, 1849-1853 (Box 475, Folder 10)
      Payment to Teachers (February & April 1852) / Receipt for Coal / Bonds
    - Brooklyn Female Academy mortgage, 1849 (Box 475, Folder 11)
    - Stockholders who gave shares of Brooklyn Female Academy, circa 1840s-1850s (Box 475, Folder 12)
      List of Brooklyn Citizens Who Gave Shares to Brooklyn Collegiate and Polytechnic Institute
    - Stock Transfer documents, 1850-1855 (Box 475, Folder 13)
      Stock Transfer Lists
    - Stock Transfer Receipts, 1851-1853 (Box 475, Folder 14)
      Brooklyn Female Academy Stock Receipts of Transfer (5 May 1851 to 18 January 1853)
    - Gifts to the Packer Collegiate Institute, 1853-1972 (Box 475, Folder 15)
    - Minard LaFever (architect) bills, 1853-1854 (Box 475, Folder 16)
      A specimen of the handwriting of Minard Lafever, the successful architect of the new school building (a receipt for architect's fees). Note that it is by mistake made out to Mr. John H. Packer instead of Mr. John H. Prentice as it should have been.
    - Stock Shareholders, 1854 (Box 475, Folder 17)
      Brooklyn Female Academy Shareholders
    - Architectural and maintenance bills, 1854 (Box 475, Folder 18)
    - Bills for furniture, 1854 (Box 475, Folder 19)
      Handwritten bills from 1850s with writing over them by Dr. Crittenden / Note explaining content of bills for furniture / with photos and map of area before Packer
    - List of gifts from Bryan H. Smith, circa 1870s (Box 475, Folder 22)
    - Tuition checks for Jane C. Hagadorn and related correspondence, 1871-1876, 1944 (Box 475, Folder 20)
      Five tuition checks from Frank Hagadorn for his daughter Jane C. Hagadorn.
    - Tuition bill for Miss Cora, 1866 (Box 554, Folder 11)
      General
      Removed from frame
    - Tuition bills, 1871-1916 (Box 475, Folder 21)
    - Receipt for tuition of Miss Ellen L. Robbins, 1875 April 14 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Building bills, 1883-1893 (Box 475, Folder 23)
    - Board of Trustees financial correspondence, 1886 (Box 475, Folder 24)
    - Property Tax bill (Block 70 - Lot 16), 1888 (Box 475, Folder 25)
    - Special pledges / donations ledger, 1890-1960 (Box 476, Folder 1)
    - Cash ledger, 1892-1904 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda for the Treasurer, regarding janitorial salary, 1893 (Box 476, Folder 2)
    - Ledger for Memorial Window Fund, 1905-1906 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - The Mrs. Packer Memorial Window Fund ledger book, 1906-1909 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Backus Memorial Fund account book, 1908-1909 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Alumnae Room leaded glass bill and acknowledgment (Mrs. James H. Post), 1911 (Box 476, Folder 3)
    - Treasurer's Reports ledger book, 1912-1922 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Letter to Miss Mary Woodward from Frank Babbott, President of Trustees, March 2, 1917 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Plea for funds letter from trustees, 1917 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Two index card boxes of Packer alumni pledge cards, 1917 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Endowment Funds, 1917-1918 (Box 476, Folder 4)
    - Endowment fund ledger, 1917-1921 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Budget ledger book, 1922-1929 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Check stubs, 1926-1932 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Budget ledger book, 1930-1934 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Letter to Mr. Roth, National City Bank, from Packer Collegiate Institute President [No Name or Signature], April 7, 1938 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Fund financial ledger, correspondence, and notes, 1944-1945 (Box 537, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Fund ledger, 1944-1947 (Box 537, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Fund Documents I, 1944-1950 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Centennial Fund Documents II, 1945-1951 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Fund contribution cards, I, 1945-1961 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Fund contribution cards, II, 1945-1961 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Budget report and other financial records, 1947-1950 (Box 476, Folder 6)
    - Gretchen (Ober) Johnson (Class of 1955) Financial receipts, 1948-1954 (Box 476, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Finance Minutes, 1951-1968 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Stock valuation, 1955 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Special pledges / donations ledger, 1956-1968 (Box 476, Folder 8)
    - 125th Anniversary Fund Ledger, 1970 (Box 476, Folder 9)
    - Financial Statements and Auditor's Report, 1994 (Box 476, Folder 12)
  - Sub-series 7.3: Pension Fund Committee, 1912-1969; 0.4 Cubic Feet in seven folders
    This sub-series is composed of material regarding the Emery Pension Fund, created by Mary M. Emery in memory of Adeline L. Jones in 1945 with a $50,000 gift in bonds to be used for the payment of pensions to retired teachers of Packer. Included is correspondence regarding wording and modification of the fund, and copies of resolutions passed the Board of Trustees. The series also contains correspondence and meeting minutes regarding pensions 1928-1943; Pension Committee meeting documents, 1912-1969; and a retirement plan proposal, 1940.
    - Emery Pension Fund, 1914-1924 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Pension Committee, 1912-1927 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Pension Committee, 1930 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Pension Committee, 1928-1943 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Pension Committee, I, 1940-1969 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Pension Committee, II, 1940-1969 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Retirement Plan Proposal, 1940 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Series 8: Student Life, 1837-2016
  The series contains an assortment of material relating to students at Packer Collegiate Institute and the Brooklyn Female Academy, dating from 1837 to 2016. It includes numerous student publications, student notebooks and scrapbooks, student handbooks, directories, diplomas, and an extensive collection of theater production files.
  The series is organized into seven sub-series:
  Sub-series 8.1: Student publications
  Sub-series 8.2: Student work, scrapbooks, and other files
  Sub-series 8.3: Packer Theater
  Sub-series 8.4: Student Handbooks and Study Guides
  Sub-series 8.5: Individual students
  Sub-series 8.6: Student Directories
  Sub-series 8.7: Diplomas and Scholarship Certificates
  - Sub-series 8.1: Student publications, 1849-2016; 16.1 Cubic Feet in thirty two boxes
    Arranged alphabetically by title, then chronologically. The word "Packer" is ignored for arrangement purposes.
    The sub-series contains assorted student publications, dating from 1849 to 2016.
    All True Tales (autobiographical comics, 1988)
    Celadon (literary magazine, 1988)
    Compositions (literary magazine, 1859-1867)
    Packer Current Items (literary magazine, 1909-2014)
    Packer '90/Packer Fagots (literary magazine, 1889-1895)
    The First Act (student newspaper, 1921-1922)
    The Kumquat (humor newspaper, 2003)
    The Literary Novice (Brooklyn Heights Seminary literary magazine, 1854)
    Middle School Poetry Anthology (literary magazine, 1987)
    The Neophyte (literary magazine, 1860-1861)
    PALM: Packer Alternative Literary Magazine (literary magazine, 1990s)
    Pelican Brief (arts and entertainment magazine, 2004-2005)
    The Packer Pen (literary magazine, 1964-1967)
    The Packer Perspective (writings from Headmaster Peter T. Esty and students on curriculum, 1971-1972)
    The Packer Press (student newspaper, 1953-1968)
    The Phoenix (literary magazine, 1867-1868)
    Picturae Clair Instituti (Class of 1896 publication)
    The Packer Prism (student newspaper, 1968-2016)
    Packer Publishers (literary magazine, 1990)
    The Packer Quarterly (literary magazine, 1868-1879)
    School Room Echoes (literary magazine, 1853)
    Serious Stuff and None of That Fake Psychedelic Crap (zine, 1989)
    Something Normal (zine, 1986)
    Underwater: A Collection of Middle School Poetry (literary magazine, 1988)
    Variations (foreign language publication, 2005-circa 2010)
    Issues of The Literary Novice from the Brooklyn Heights Seminary are dated May 19, October 6, October 30, November 3, November 17, and December 15, 1854. These issues were sent to Mrs. Harold Quantin at Packer in 1943.
    Packer Current Items was first published in 1909 – a copy of vol. 1, issue 1 is included in this series. The publication continued into the twenty-first century, marking it as the longest-running student publication at Packer. Date, volume and issue numbers are sometimes inconsistent. A few issues are missing (see container list for details). Also included in this series is correspondence from various alumni regarding the 50th anniversary issue of Packer Current Items, which was celebrated in 1959.
    - All True Tales (3 copies), circa 1988 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Celadon, 1988 (Box 497, Folder 3)
    - Collective Poems, 2004 (Box 497, Folder 4)
    - Compositions - Bound volume 2, 1859-1867 (Box 497, Folder 5)
      Includes President's addresses, circulars, school floor plans, and other items
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 1, no. 1, November (1 copy) First issue, very brittle, heavy spine damage and some cover tears, 1909 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 1, no. 2-3, 1910 (Box 497, Folder 6)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 2, no. 6 and 8, 1911 (Box 497, Folder 7)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 3, no. 9-10, 1911-1912 (Box 497, Folder 8)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 4, no. 13, November (1 copy), 1912 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 5, no. 1, 1913 (Box 497, Folder 9)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 8, no. 3, 1917 (Box 497, Folder 10)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 9, no. 1, 1917 (Box 498, Folder 1)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 9, no. 1, November (1 copy), 1916 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 9, no. 2, December (1 copy) Includes a note dated 1991, addressed to board of trustees from Jayne & George King and Ann & Jim Wilson donating issues of Packer Current Items owned by their mother, Hilma Jayne Wilson, class of 1917., 1916 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 9, no. 2, 1918 (Box 498, Folder 2)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 9, no. 3, February (1 copy), 1917 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 9, no. 3, 1918 (Box 498, Folder 3)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 9, no. 4, 1918 (Box 498, Folder 4)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 10, no. 1-3, 1918-1919 (Box 498, Folder 5)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 10, no. 3, April (1 copy), 1919 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 10, no. 4, June (2 copies), 1919 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 11, no. 1-4, 1919-1920 (Box 498, Folder 6)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 11, no. 1, November (2 copies), 1919 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 11, no. 4, June (1 copy), 1920 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 12, no. 1-5, 1920-1921 (Box 498, Folder 7)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 12, no. 1, November (1 copy), 1920 (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 12, no. 4, March (1 copy), 1921 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 12, no. 5, April (1 copy), 1921 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 13, no. 1, 3-5, 1921-1922 (Box 498, Folder 8)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 13, no. 1, November (1 copy), 1921 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 13, no. 2, December (2 copies), 1921 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 13, no. 3, February (1 copy), 1922 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 13, no. 6, June (2 copies), 1922 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 14, no. 1, November (2 copies), 1922 (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 14, no. 2, 4-5, 1922-1923 (Box 498, Folder 9)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 14, no. 2, December (1 copy), 1922 (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 14, no. 3, February (2 copies), 1923 (Box 121, Folder 20)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 14, no. 6, June (2 copies), 1923 (Box 121, Folder 21)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 15, no. 1, 3-6, 1923-1924 (Box 498, Folder 10)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 15, no. 2, December (3 copies), 1923 (Box 121, Folder 22)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 15, no. 3, February (1 copy), 1924 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 15, no. 6, June (1 copy), 1924 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 16, no. 1-6, 1924-1925 (Box 498, Folder 11)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 16, no. 4, Spring (1 copy), 1925 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 17, no. 1, 1925 (Box 560, Folder 5)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 17, no. 1-4, 1925-1926 (Box 499, Folder 1)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 17, no. 5-6, 1926 (Box 499, Folder 2)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 18, no. 1-4, 1926-1927 (Box 499, Folder 3)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 18, no. 16, June (2 copies), 1927 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 19, no. 1-6, 1927-1928 (Box 499, Folder 4)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 19, no. 2, December (1 copy), 1927 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 19, no. 3, February (1 copy), 1928 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 19, no. 4, March (1 copy), 1928 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 19, no. 6, December (1 copy), 1928 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 20, no. 1-5, 1928-1929 (Box 499, Folder 5)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 20, no. 4, April (1 copy), 1929 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 20, no. 5, June (1 copy), 1929 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 21, no. 1-4, 1929-1930 (Box 499, Folder 6)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 21, no. 1, November (1 copy), 1929 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 21, no. 3, March (1 copy), 1930 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 21, no. 4, April (1 copy), 1930 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 22, no. 1-5, 1930-1931 (Box 499, Folder 7)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 22, no. 1, November (1 copy), 1930 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 22, no. 2, December (1 copy), 1930 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 22, no. 5, June (1 copy), 1931 (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 23, no. 1, 1931 (Box 499, Folder 8)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 23, no. 2, December (1 copy), 1931 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 23, no. 3, March (1 copy), 1932 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 23, no. 4, April (1 copy), 1932 (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 23, no. 5, 1932 (Box 499, Folder 9)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 23, no. 5, June (1 copy), 1932 (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 24, no. 1, November (1 copy), 1932 (Box 122, Folder 21)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 24, no. 2, December (1 copy), 1932 (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 24, no. 3, February (1 copy), 1933 (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 24, no. 4, April (1 copy), 1933 (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 24, no. 5, May (1 copy), 1933 (Box 122, Folder 25)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 25, no. 1-4, 1933-1934 (Box 499, Folder 10)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 25, no. 2, December (1 copy), 1933 (Box 122, Folder 26)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 25, no. 5, June (1 copy), 1934 (Box 122, Folder 27)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 26, no. 1, 1934 (Box 560, Folder 5)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 26, no. 1-4, 1934-1935 (Box 500, Folder 1)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 27, no. 2-5, 1935-1936 (Box 500, Folder 2)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 28, no. 1, 3-5, 1936-1937 (Box 500, Folder 3)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 28, no. 1, November (1 copy), 1936 (Box 122, Folder 28)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 28, no. 2-5, 1937-1938 (Box 500, Folder 4)
      Volume 28 used for two volumes consecutively
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 28, no. 2, December (3 copies), 1936 (Box 122, Folder 29)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 28, no. 3, March (1 copy), 1937 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 28, no. 4, April (1 copy), 1937 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 28, no. 5, June (1 copy), 1937 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 28, no. 6, Autumn (2 copies), 1937 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 28, no. 2 [misnumbered], December (1 copy), 1937 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 28, no. 3 [misnumbered], March (1 copy), 1938 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 29, no. 1-2, 4-5, 1938-1939 (Box 500, Folder 5)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 29, no. 1, November (1 copy), 1938 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 29, no. 2, December (1 copy), 1938 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Packer Current Items, vol. 29, no. 3, March (2 copies), 1939 (Box 123, Folder 9)